<resources>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment" translatable="false">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="onBoardingTitle">Welcome to the Visa Application</string>
    <string name="onBoarding1_SubTitle">
        With the Visa Application, obtaining your electronic visa has become incredibly easy, whether it\'s a tourist visa, employment visa, or company visa. Don\'t worry about the exhausting procedures; we have a complete team working for your convenience.</string>
    <string name="onBoarding2_subTitle">Whether you are looking for a job or you are one of the owners of companies looking for employment, a team of experts will be at your service at the highest level, just fill out your form with easy steps without complications</string>
    <string name="onBoarding3_subTitle">You can reach your favorite destination anywhere in the world just prepare for your trip and leave the rest to us and enjoy a smooth and safe experience of obtaining your tourist visa</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">Al Tasherat</string>
    <string name="altasherat_platform">Altasherat Platform</string>
    <string name="error_no_internet">Couldn\'t connect to server, please check your internet connection.</string>
    <string name="error_unknown">Something went wrong. Please try again later.</string>
    <string name="error_serialization">Couldn\'t serialize or deserialize data.</string>
    <string name="error_internal_server">Internal server error with code:%d, and the failure reason: %s</string>
    <string name="error_bad_request">The request was malformed or invalid. Please check your input and try again.</string>
    <string name="error_unauthorized">You are not authorized to access this resource. Please log in and try again.</string>
    <string name="error_forbidden">Access to this resource is forbidden. You do not have the required permissions.</string>
    <string name="error_not_found">The requested resource could not be found. Please check the URL or try again later.</string>
    <string name="error_unknown_http">An unexpected error occurred (HTTP %1$d). Please try again later or contact support.</string>
    <string name="error_io">An I/O error occurred while accessing local storage</string>
    <string name="error_data_corruption">Data corruption detected in local storage</string>
    <string name="error_type_mismatch">Unsupported data type for local storage</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="continue_txt">Continue</string>
    <string name="please_choose_language_txt">Please Choose Language</string>
    <string name="please_choose_country_txt">Please Choose Country</string>
    <string name="you_can_change_your_country_or_language_any_time_from_menu">You can change your country or language any time from menu</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->


</resources>